Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Annotated, not numbered
      - M-O
        - Moses, Pablo - Pave the way, 1981; SR-25832; Moses, Pablo (Box 54)
          Mango
        - MOT - Mellow; 97 winks; 110 mistakes, 1998; SR-25833; MOT (Box 54)
          Catalog # 314-570 285-1; A-side Matrix # 314-520-285-1 A
        - Mother's Finest - Iron age, 1981; SR-25834; Mother's Finest (Box 54)
          Catalog # SD 19302; A-side Matrix # STA 814677-A
        - Mother's Finest - Another mother further, 1977; SR-25835; Mother's Finest (Box 54)
          Catalog # PE 34699; A-side Matrix # BL-34699-1A
          Epic
        - Mother's Finest - Mother's Finest live, 1979; SR-25836; Mother's Finest (Box 54)
          Catalog # EPC 83693; A-side Matrix # 01-83693-2A-2
        - Mother's Finest - Mother's Finest live, 1979; SR-25837; Mother's Finest (Box 54)
          Catalog # JE 35976; A-side Matrix # AL 35976-1B
        - Motorbass - Ezio, 1998; SR-25838; Motorbass (Box 54)
          Catalog # ALE 000; A-side Matrix # ALE 000 A
          Motorbass
        - Motown Magic Disco Machine - Motown Magic Disco Machine volume II, 1976; SR-25839; Motown Magic Disco Machine (Box 54)
          Catalog # 2575-S; A-side Matrix # M-857P1-S1
          Ontario, Canada
        - Motta, Ed - Entre e ouça, 1992; SR-25840; Motta, Ed (Box 54)
          Catalog # 670 8252; A-side Matrix # 670.8252-A
          Rio de Janeiro, Brazil
        - Motta, Ed - Dwitza, 2002; SR-25841; Motta, Ed (Box 54)
          Catalog # WMLP-0018; A-side Matrix # B259125-01 A1 MK
          Whatmusic.com
        - Moutouari, Pierre - Tumba, 1982; SR-25842; Moutouari, Pierre (Box 54)
          Catalog # 9506; A-side Matrix # MELO-9505A
          H.K.Productions
        - Moutouari, Pierre - Tumba, 1982; SR-25843; Moutouari, Pierre (Box 54)
        - Mouzon, Alphonse - Virtue, 1980; SR-25844; Mouzon, Alphonse (Box 54)
          Catalog # PR 7054; A-side Matrix # PR 7054 A
          Pausa Records
        - Mouzon, Alphonse - Mind transplant, 1975; SR-25845; Mouzon, Alphonse (Box 54)
          Catalog # BN-LA398-G; A-side Matrix # BN-LA 398-1RE1
        - Mowatt, Judy - Only a woman, 1982; SR-25846; Mowatt, Judy (Box 54)
          Catalog # SHANACHIE-43007; A-side Matrix # SH-43007-A
          Shanachie Records
          Newton, New Jersey
        - M'pouly, Peter - Africa la mal aimée, 1988; SR-25847; M'pouly, Peter (Box 54)
          Catalog # MP 001; A-side Matrix # MP001A
        - Mr. Low Kash "n" Da Shady Bunch - Whoo huhh, 2000; SR-25848; Mr. Low Kash "n" Da Shady Bunch (Box 54)
          Catalog # PP 53912; A-side Matrix # S-33891 RE-1
          Pep Records
          Jersey City, New Jersey
        - Mr. Mix - Make ya boy holla, 1994; SR-25849; Mr. Mix; Da Roughneck Posse (Box 54)
          Catalog # OTR-5005; A-side Matrix # OTR-5005-G1A A
          Otown Records
        - Mr. Reds - Bring the lights down (remixes), 2000; SR-25850; Mr. Reds; Kalibre (Box 54)
          Catalog # ICE 002; A-side Matrix # ICE 002 A
          Ice Cold
        - Mr. Smith - Mr. Smith's DJ tools #3, 2001; SR-25851; Mr. Smith (Box 54)
          Catalog # 6614-MR003-1; A-side Matrix # 6614-MR003-1 (A)
          Mr. Smith's DJ Tools
        - Mr. Smith - Mr. Smith's DJ tools #1, 2001; SR-25852; Mr. Smith (Box 54)
          Catalog # 6614-MR001-1; A-side Matrix # 6614-MR001-1 (A)
        - Mr. X & Mr. Y - Respect, 1988; SR-25853; Mr. X & Mr. Y (Box 54)
          In same jacket as # SR-25854. 2 copies.
          Catalog # GF 12002; A-side Matrix # GF-12002-A
          G Fine Sounds
        - Mr. X & Mr. Y - Respect, 1988; SR-25854; Mr. X & Mr. Y (Box 54)
          In same jacket as # SR-25853. 2 copies.
        - Mtume - Juicy fruit, 1983; SR-25855; Mtume (Box 54)
          Catalog # FE 38588; A-side Matrix # PAL 38588-2A
        - Mtume - Theater of the mind, 1986; SR-25856; Mtume (Box 54)
          Catalog # E 40262; A-side Matrix # AL-40262-1B-1
        - Mtume - You, me and he, 1984; SR-25857; Mtume (Box 54)
          In same jacket as # SR-25858. Different discs.
          Catalog # FE 39473; A-side Matrix # PAL 39473-1B
        - Mtume - C.O.D. (I'll deliver), 1984; SR-25858; Mtume (Box 54)
          In same jacket as # SR-25857. Different discs.
          Catalog # 49-05116; A-side Matrix # XSS-173031-A
        - Muhammad, Idris - Boogie boots; Foxhuntin', 1979; SR-25859; Muhammad, Idris (Box 54)
          Catalog # D-136; A-side Matrix # D 136-A-RE1-1A
        - Muhammad, Idris - Make it count, 1980; SR-25860; Muhammad, Idris (Box 54)
          In same jacket as # SR-27000. Different discs.
          Catalog # F-9598; A-side Matrix # F 9598 A RE1-1A
        - Muhammad, Idris - For your love, 1980; SR-27000; Muhammad, Idris (Box 54)
          In same jacket as # SR-25860. Different discs.
          Catalog # D-159; A-side Matrix # D 159 A
        - Mundell, Hugh - Jah fire, 1980; SR-27001; Mundell, Hugh (Box 54)
          Catalog # ARIL LP 001; A-side Matrix # ARK LP 001 B
          Arawak
        - Munich Machine - Body shine, 1979; SR-27002; Munich Machine (Box 54)
          Catalog # NBLP 7137; A-side Matrix # NBLP-7137-AS-RE-1
        - Murdock, Shirley - Shirley Murdock!, 1985; SR-27003; Murdock, Shirley (Box 54)
          Catalog # 60443-1; A-side Matrix # STE-60443-A
        - Murphy, Eddie - How could it be, 1985; SR-27004; Murphy, Eddie (Box 54)
          Catalog # FC 39952; A-side Matrix # PAL-39952-1A
        - Murphy, Walter - Phantom of the opera, 1978; SR-27005; Murphy, Walter (Box 54)
          Catalog # PS 7010; A-side Matrix # PS 7010A
          Private Stock
        - Muscle Shoals Horns - Shine on, 1983; SR-27006; Muscle Shoals Horns (Box 54)
          Catalog # FW 38530; A-side Matrix # FW-38530-AS-1A
          Monument
        - Musical Youth - Different style!, 1983; SR-27007; Musical Youth (Box 55)
          Catalog # MCA-5454; A-side Matrix # MCA-3663-FDS-1
        - Musical Youth - The youth of today, 1982; SR-27008; Musical Youth (Box 55)
          Catalog # YOULP 1; A-side Matrix # YOU-LP-1-A2
        - Mutabaruka - Check it!, 1983; SR-27009; Mutabaruka (Box 55)
          Catalog # AL 8306; A-side Matrix # AL-8306-A
          Alligator Records
        - Mutiny - Funk plus the one, 1980; SR-27010; Mutiny (Box 55)
          Catalog # JC 36597; A-side Matrix # AL 36597-1A
        - Myers, Alicia - Spirit of the boogie, 1981; SR-27011; Myers, Alicia (Box 55)
          Catalog # L33-1718; A-side Matrix # MCA 2610
        - Myron - We can get down, 1997; SR-27012; Myron (Box 55)
          Catalog # 314-572 065-1; A-side Matrix # 314-572-065-1-A
        - Nasa - Insha-Allah!, 1990; SR-27013; Nasa (Box 55)
          Catalog # 1-26008; A-side Matrix # 1-26008-A-SR1
        - Native - In a strange land, 1981; SR-27014; Native (Box 55)
          Catalog # AFL1-3992; A-side Matrix # AFL1-3992-A-10S
        - Native Son - Native Son, 1979; SR-27015; Native Son (Box 55)
          Catalog # INF 9022; A-side Matrix # INF-9022-A-AZ-1
          Infinity Records
        - Natural Elements - 2 tons; Live it up, 1999; SR-27016; Natural Elements (Box 55)
          In same jacket as # SR-27017. 2 copies.
          Catalog # TB 495; A-side Matrix # TB-0495-A
          Tommy Boy Black Label
        - Natural Elements - 2 tons; Live it up, 1999; SR-27017; Natural Elements (Box 55)
          In same jacket as # SR-27016. 2 copies.
        - Nature's Creation - Freak unique, 1985; SR-27018; Nature's Creation (Box 55)
          Catalog # CCR-000; A-side Matrix # CCR-000-A
          Capital City Records
        - Nature's Divine - In the beginning, 1979; SR-27019; Nature's Divine (Box 55)
          Catalog # INF 9013; A-side Matrix # INS-9013-A-AT-1
        - Nava, Mariella - Per paura o per amore, 1988; SR-27020; Nava, Mariella (Box 55)
          Catalog # PL 71665; A-side Matrix # PL 71665-A
        - Nazareth - Malice in wonderland, 1980; SR-27021; Nazareth (Box 55)
          Catalog # SP-4799; A-side Matrix # AM SP 4799-A RE-2
        - Nazario, Ednita - Vete, vete, 1977; SR-27022; Nazario, Ednita (Box 55)
          Catalog # AAD 1324; A-side Matrix # AAD-1324-A
          Borinquen
          San Juan, Puerto Rico
        - N.B.A. - "Ghetto anthem" the Scooby Doo joint, 2002; SR-27023; N.B.A.; New Black America (Box 55)
          In same jacket as # SR-27024. 2 copies.
          Catalog # KOK-4; A-side Matrix # KOK-4 A
          King of Klub
          Baltimore, Maryland
        - N.B.A. - "Ghetto anthem" the Scooby Doo joint, 2002; SR-27024; N.B.A.; New Black America (Box 55)
          In same jacket as # SR-27023. 2 copies.
        - Ndugu & the Chocoloate Jam Co. - Shadow dancing, 1980; SR-27025; Ndugu & the Chocoloate Jam Co.; Chancler, Ndugu; Chocolate Jam Company (Box 55)
          Catalog # AS 727; A-side Matrix # XSS-166546-1C
        - Ndugu & the Chocoloate Jam Co. - Do I make you feel better?, 1980; SR-27026; Ndugu & the Chocoloate Jam Co.; Chancler, Ndugu; Chocolate Jam Company (Box 55)
          Catalog # JE 36377; A-side Matrix # PAL-36377-1G
        - Neal, Pamela - Charlie Hustle, 1979; SR-27027; Neal, Pamela (Box 55)
          Catalog # JD-11556; A-side Matrix # PD-11556-A
          Free Flight
        - Negro, J Walter - Shoot the pump, 1981; SR-27028; Negro, J Walter; Loose Jointz (Box 55)
          Catalog # 4W9-2473; A-side Matrix # 4W9-2473-A
          Zoo York Records
        - Nelly - Nellyville (disc one), 2002; SR-27029; Nelly (Box 55)
          In same jacket as # SR-27030. Double album.
          Catalog # 440 017 747-1; A-side Matrix # 440 017 747-1A EP1
        - Nelly - Nellyville (disc two), 2002; SR-27030; Nelly (Box 55)
          In same jacket as # SR-27029. Double album.
          Catalog # 440 017 747-1; A-side Matrix # 440 017 747-1A LP2
        - Nelson, Sandy - Let there be drums, 1962; SR-27031; Nelson, Sandy (Box 55)
          Catalog # LP-12080; A-side Matrix # LP-12080-1
          United Artists Records
        - Neon Judgement - Horny as hell, 1987; SR-27032; Neon Judgement (Box 55)
          Catalog # BIUS 1005; A-side Matrix # BIUS-1005-A
          Play It Again Sam Records USA
        - Neosoul - Introfusion, 1998; SR-27033; Neosoul (Box 55)
          Catalog # ORBIT 006; A-side Matrix # OT-006-A
          Orbit Transmission Records
          Southern California
        - Nelson - The chief breakin for '85, 1985; SR-27034; Nelson (Box 55)
          Catalog #; A-side Matrix # N-452-A
          MRS Records
        - Nelson - We like it..., 1982; SR-27035; Nelson (Box 55)
          Catalog # BSR 1034; A-side Matrix # 1034-A
        - Nelson, Lord - Gimme something, 1986; SR-27036; Nelson, Lord (Box 55)
          Catalog # NCR 384; A-side Matrix # NCR-384-RE1-A
        - N*E*R*D - In search of... (disc one), 2002; SR-27037; N*E*R*D (Box 55)
          In same jacket as # SR-27038. Double album.
          Catalog # 7243 8 12622 1 4; A-side Matrix # XAR12622-1ARE1
        - N*E*R*D - In search of... (disc two), 2002; SR-27038; N*E*R*D (Box 55)
          In same jacket as # SR-27037. Double album.
          Catalog # 7243 8 12622 1 4; A-side Matrix # XAR12622-1C
        - Netto's Bzar - Loz Netto's Bzar, 1982; SR-27039; Netto's Bzar (Box 55)
          Catalog # 2-111; A-side Matrix # 2111-A11 51765-1-1
          21 Records
        - Nevil, Robbie - Robbie Nevil, 1986; SR-27040; Nevil, Robbie (Box 55)
          Catalog # ST-53006; A-side Matrix # ST 1 53006 Z1
          Manhattan Records
        - Neville Brothers - Treacherous: a history of the Neville Brothers (disc one), 1986; SR-27041; Neville Brothers (Box 55)
          In same jacket as # SR-27042. Double album.
          Catalog # RNFP 71494; A-side Matrix # RNFP-71494A
          Rhino Records
        - Neville Brothers - Treacherous: a history of the Neville Brothers (disc two), 1986; SR-27042; Neville Brothers (Box 55)
          In same jacket as # SR-27041. Double album.
          Catalog # RNFP 71494; A-side Matrix # RNFP-71494C
        - New Birth - Platinum city, 1979; SR-27043; New Birth (Box 55)
          In same jacket as # SR-27044. 2 copies.
          Catalog # SW-50062; A-side Matrix # SW-50062-A
          Ariola Records
          Beverly Hills, California
        - New Birth - Platinum city, 1979; SR-27044; New Birth (Box 55)
          In same jacket as # SR-27043. 2 copies.
        - New Birth - I'm back, 1982; SR-27045; New Birth (Box 55)
          Catalog # AFL1-4411; A-side Matrix # AFL-1-4411-A
        - New Direction - The New Direction, 1970; SR-27046; New Direction (Box 55)
          Catalog # XCSV-142594; A-side Matrix # NLPS-200
          Neptune Records
        - New Kids on the Block - New Kids on the Block, 1986; SR-27047; New Kids on the Block (Box 55)
          Catalog # C 40475; A-side Matrix # AL 40475-1A
        - New Marketts - Step on it, 1977; SR-27048; New Marketts (Box 55)
          Catalog # CAL 7003; A-side Matrix # CAL-7003-A-1A
          Calliope
          Sherman Oaks, California
        - New Order - Ceremony, 1981; SR-27049; New Order (Box 55)
          Catalog # FAC 33; A-side Matrix # FAC 33 A
          Factory
        - New Tony Williams Lifetime - Million dollar legs, 1976; SR-27050; New Tony Williams Lifetime (Box 55)
          Catalog # PC 34263; A-side Matrix # PAL-34263
        - New Toys - Say it, 1982; SR-27051; New Toys (Box 55)
          Catalog # MC 20186; A-side Matrix # MC 20186A
          Playtime Records
          Clarence, New York
        - New Version of Soul - Birth of the souladelic, 1993; SR-27052; New Version of Soul (Box 55)
          Catalog # SPRO-79680; A-side Matrix # SPRO 79680Z1
        - New York Citi Peech Boys - Life is something special, 1982; SR-27053; New York Citi Peech Boys (Box 55)
          Catalog # 0-99928; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-43945-43946-1
        - New York Style - Running, 1994; SR-27054; New York Style (Box 55)
          Catalog # MIC-597; A-side Matrix # MIC-597-A
          Micmac Records
        - Newberry, Booker III - Love town (long version); Doin' what comes naturally, 1983; SR-27055; Newberry, Booker III (Box 55)
          Catalog # NB-99905-9; A-side Matrix # NB-AL-99905-9
          The Boardwalk Entertainment Co
        - Newcleus - Jam on revenge, 1984; SR-27056; Newcleus (Box 55)
          Catalog # SUN 4901; A-side Matrix # SUN 4901-A
          Sunnyview
        - Newtrapment - London Bridge is falling down (extended version), 1983; SR-27057; Newtrapment (Box 55)
          In same jacket as # SR-27058. 2 copies.
          Catalog # JIVE T 43; A-side Matrix # JIVE T 43 A1
          Jive
        - Newtrapment - London Bridge is falling down (extended version), 1983; SR-27058; Newtrapment (Box 55)
          In same jacket as # SR-27057. 2 copies.
        - Newtrons - The Newtrons, 1990; SR-27059; Newtrons (Box 56)
          Catalog # MCA-6381; A-side Matrix # MCA-9660 FDS-1
        - Next - Too close, 1997; SR-27060; Next (Box 56)
          Catalog # 07822-13457-1; A-side Matrix # 07822-13457-1-SA
        - Next - Welcome II nextasy (disc one), 1999; SR-27061; Next (Box 56)
          In same jacket as # SR-27062. Double album.
          Catalog # 07822-14643-1; A-side Matrix # 07822-14643-1SA
        - Next - Welcome II nextasy (disc two), 1999; SR-27062; Next (Box 56)
          In same jacket as # SR-27061. Double album.
          Catalog # 07822-14643-1; A-side Matrix # 07822-14643-1SC
        - Nice & Smooth - IV: blazing hot, 1997; SR-27063; Nice & Smooth (Box 56)
          Catalog # 72392 75534-1; A-side Matrix # 72392-75534-1 A
          Street Life Records
        - Nice and Wild - Energy, love and unity, 1987; SR-27064; Nice and Wild (Box 56)
          Catalog # 81719-1; A-side Matrix # ST-A-866261-A
        - Niccodeemos - Dance hall style, 1982; SR-27065; Niccodeemos (Box 56)
          Catalog # DHLP 2003; A-side Matrix # DHLP 2003-A1
          Black Joy
        - Nicodemus - DJ clash, 1982; SR-27066; Nicodemus; Toyan (Box 56)
          Catalog # GREL 32; A-side Matrix # GREL 32A1
        - Nicodemus - The very best of Nicodemus, 1983; SR-27067; Nicodemus (Box 56)
          Catalog # SG 8001; A-side Matrix # SG-8001-A
          Serious Gold
        - Nigger Kojak - Rock jack Kojak, 1983; SR-27068; Nigger Kojak (Box 56)
          Catalog # NKLP 002; A-side Matrix # LIVE AT PRINCE JAMMY'S-A
          Nigger Kojak
        - Night - Long distance, 1980; SR-27069; Night (Box 56)
          Catalog # P-10; A-side Matrix # P-10-A-RE-SP
          Planet Records
        - Nightingale, Tunde - Gbogungboro! "Ojiji omo a f'ojiji pi", 1980; SR-27070; Nightingale, Tunde (Box 56)
          Catalog # JRFM-1; A-side Matrix # JRFM-1A
          Fisher Music
        - Night People - Again, 1980; SR-27071; Night People (Box 56)
          Catalog # TS 2001; A-side Matrix # TS-2001A-1B
          The Sound of Brooklyn Records
        - Nightlife Unlimited - Nightlife Unlimited, 1979; SR-27072; Nightlife Unlimited (Box 56)
          Catalog # NBLP 7139; A-side Matrix # NBLP-7139-AS-KL1
        - Nights - The Nights, 1976; SR-27073; Nights (Box 56)
          Catalog # AB-1033; A-side Matrix # AB-1033-A
        - Nights - The Nights, 1976; SR-27074; Nights (Box 56)
          Catalog # LSLP-1003; A-side Matrix # LSLP-1003-A
          Little Star Records
        - Niteflyte - Niteflyte, 1979; SR-27075; Niteflyte (Box 56)
          Catalog # SW-50060; A-side Matrix # SW-50060 A/S
          Ariola Records America
        - Nitzinger - Live better electrically, 1976; SR-27076; Nitzinger (Box 56)
          Catalog # T-518; A-side Matrix # M-518-AS-RE1
          20th Century Records
        - No Good - Lizard-lizard (disc one), 1998; SR-27077; No Good; Jiggie (Box 56)
          In same jacket as # SR-27078. Double album.
          Catalog # 07863-67744-1; A-side Matrix # 07863-67744-1-A
          Loud Records
        - No Good - Lizard-lizard (disc two), 1998; SR-27078; No Good; Jiggie (Box 56)
          In same jacket as # SR-27077. Double album.
          Catalog # 07863-67744-1; A-side Matrix # 07863-67744-1-C
        - North End - Kind of life (kind of love), 1979; SR-27079; North End (Box 56)
          Catalog # WES DJ 22125; A-side Matrix # 70420-22124-A
          West End records
        - North, Ian - Rape of orchids, 1982; SR-27080; North, Ian (Box 56)
          Catalog # PHEP 1100; A-side Matrix # MX-001-A-RE
          Neo Records
        - Miami - Notorious Miami, 1976; SR-27081; Miami (Box 56)
          Catalog # DRIVE 102; A-side Matrix # DRIVE-102-A
          Drive
        - November Group - November Group, 1982; SR-27082; November Group (Box 56)
          Catalog # MM015; A-side Matrix # MM-015-A
          Modern Method Records
          Boston, Massachusetts
        - N.S.O. Force Organisation - Give it up, 1989; SR-27083; N.S.O. Force Organisation (Box 56)
          Catalog # STORM 10; A-side Matrix # STORM 10 A2
          Vinyl Solution
        - Nu Shooz - Poolside, 1986; SR-27084; Nu Shooz (Box 56)
          Catalog # 81647-1; A-side Matrix # ST A 865961-A
        - Numan, Gary - The plan, 1984; SR-27085; Numan, Gary; Tubeway Army (Box 56)
          Catalog # BEGA 55; A-side Matrix # BEGA-55-A1
          Beggars Banquet
        - Numan, Gary - I, assassin, 1982; SR-27086; Numan, Gary (Box 56)
          Catalog # 90014-1; A-side Matrix # ST-C-825025-C
          ATCO Records
        - Numan, Gary - Dance, 1981; SR-27087; Numan, Gary (Box 56)
          Catalog # SD 38-143; A-side Matrix # ST-C814787-C
        - Numan, Gary - Warriors, 1983; SR-27088; Numan, Gary (Box 56)
          Catalog # 24-0241-1; A-side Matrix # BEGA-47-A-240241-1-AX
        - Numan, Gary - Berserker, 1984; SR-27089; Numan, Gary (Box 56)
          Catalog # NUMA 1001; A-side Matrix # NUMA-1001-A1
          Numa
          Shepperton, United Kingdom
        - Numan, Gary - White noise (disc one), 1985; SR-27090; Numan, Gary (Box 56)
          In same jacket as # SR-27091. Double album.
          Catalog # NUMAD 1002; A-side Matrix # NUMAD-1002-A1
        - Numan, Gary - White noise (disc two), 1985; SR-27091; Numan, Gary (Box 56)
          In same jacket as # SR-27090. Double album.
          Catalog # NUMAD 1002; A-side Matrix # NUMAD-1002-C1
        - Nunn, Bobby - Private party, 1983; SR-27092; Nunn, Bobby (Box 56)
          In same jacket as # SR-27093. Different discs.
          Catalog # 6051ML; A-side Matrix # 6051ML-A-15A
        - Nunn, Bobby - Private party, 1983; SR-27093; Nunn, Bobby (Box 56)
          In same jacket as # SR-27092. Different discs.
          Catalog # PR-127; A-side Matrix # PR127B-66861-DI-15B
        - Nunn, Bobby - Second to Nunn, 1982; SR-27094; Nunn, Bobby (Box 56)
          In same jacket as # SR-27095. Different discs.
          Catalog # 6022ML-RE-2; A-side Matrix # 6022ML-A-RE2-15G
        - Nunn, Bobby - Got to get up on it, 1982; SR-27095; Nunn, Bobby (Box 56)
          In same jacket as # SR-27094. Different discs.
          Catalog # PR-111; A-side Matrix # PR111A-66653-D-15A
        - Nuyorican Soul - I am black gold of the sun (disc two), 1997; SR-27096; Nuyorican Soul (Box 56)
          In same jacket as # SR-27097. 2 copies.
          Catalog # GOLD2; A-side Matrix # GOLD2A
          Talkin' Loud
        - Nuyorican Soul - I am black gold of the sun (disc two), 1997; SR-27097; Nuyorican Soul (Box 56)
          In same jacket as # SR-27096. 2 copies.
        - Nuyorican Soul - I am black gold of the sun (disc one), 1997; SR-27098; Nuyorican Soul (Box 56)
          In same jacket as # SR-27099. 2 copies.
          Catalog # GOLD1; A-side Matrix # GOLD1A
        - Nuyorican Soul - I am black gold of the sun (disc one), 1997; SR-27099; Nuyorican Soul (Box 56)
          In same jacket as # SR-27098. 2 copies.
        - N.W.A. - 100 miles and runnin', 1990; SR-27100; N.W.A. (Box 56)
          Catalog # EVL7224; A-side Matrix # EVL-1-7224-Z1
        - Nyasia - Midnight passion, 1993; SR-27101; Nyasia (Box 56)
          Catalog # MIC-590; A-side Matrix # MIC-590-A
        - NYCC - I'll keep my light in my window, 1978; SR-27102; NYCC (Box 56)
          Catalog # DJL1-2880; A-side Matrix # DJL1-2880A-1
        - NYCC - Make every day count, 1978; SR-27103; NYCC (Box 56)
          Catalog # APL1-2782; A-side Matrix # APL1-2782A-2
        - O'Connor, Sinead - The emperor's new clothes, 1990; SR-27104; O'Connor, Sinead (Box 56)
          Catalog # SPRO 23568; A-side Matrix # SPRO-23568-A-1
          Ensign
        - O'Connor, Sinead - Mandinka, 1988; SR-27105; O'Connor, Sinead (Box 56)
          Catalog # VAS 2902; A-side Matrix # VAS-2902-A
        - Odyssey - Going back to my roots, 1981; SR-27106; Odyssey (Box 56)
          In same jacket as # SR-27107. Different discs.
          Catalog # JD-12241; A-side Matrix # PD-12241-A-1
        - Odyssey - I got the melody, 1981; SR-27107; Odyssey (Box 56)
          In same jacket as # SR-27106. Different discs.
          Catalog # AFL1-3910; A-side Matrix # AFL-1-3910-15A
        - OGs - OG style volume 1, 2004; SR-27108; OGs (Box 56)
          Catalog #; A-side Matrix # 0201X28-A
        - OGs - The OGs volume 4, 2004; SR-27109; OGs (Box 56)
          In same jacket as # SR-27110. 2 copies.
          Catalog # OGSR 0004; A-side Matrix # OGSR-0004-A
          Official Ghetto Style Records
        - OGs - The OGs volume 4, 2004; SR-27110; OGs (Box 56)
          In same jacket as # SR-27109. 2 copies.
        - Oh-Bonic - Power surge, 1992; SR-27111; Oh-Bonic (Box 56)
          Catalog # CR-2003; A-side Matrix # CR 2003 LEFT
          Cutting Records
        - Ohio Players - Climax, 1974; SR-27112; Ohio Players (Box 56)
          Catalog # WB 1003; A-side Matrix # WB-1003-A
          Westbound Records
        - Ohio Players - Everybody up, 1979; SR-27113; Ohio Players (Box 57)
          Catalog # AB 4226; A-side Matrix # AB 4226 SA RE